

Ashok Arya

H.No WZ 70, Gali No. 2 Shree Nagar, Shukurpur Delhi 110034

+919027882088 | akarya1304@gmail.com

Objective

A fully trained, train the trainer, yog teacher with 10+ years of Yog teaching experience. I can help with any ailments such as Herniated Disc, Sciatica, Thyroidism (Hypo / Hyper), Blood Pressure, Anxiety, Depression etc. With consistent practice and yog classes these can be cured for good without any medications.

Experience

Rapid Creations Private limited
 Yoga Teacher

2017 - 2019

• Swami Parmanand Parkartik Chikitsalya Yoga & Anusandhan Kendra, West Vinod Nagar New Delhi 2019 - 2020

Yoga Therapist

• Home Yoga Classess as a Freelancer Yoga Teacher 2014 - 2024

2018

Education

- Jain Vishav Bharati Institute of Ladnun
 M.A in Yoga & Science of Living
 68.10%
- Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan
 One Year Diploma in Yoga Vidya
 70%
- Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan
 Six Months Certificate in Yoga Vidya
 67.8
- Morarji Desai National Institute of Yoga
 Certificate Course in Yogasana

Skills

- Physical skills
- Versatility Adaptability
- Stress Management
- Breathing Techniques
- Creativity Self Motivation
- · CPR, First aid
- Knowledge of Anatomy
- Mentoring Commission
- Time Manegement